ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials
1969- 2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4283 AV
30.67 cubic feet
30.7 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
This collection is made up of VHS, cassette tapes, DVDs, Umatic tapes, 16mm film, etc., training material that deal with workplace issues.
6876497
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 03, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 28, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4062m: ILR School Extension Division Albany Office Correspondence /4063: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4103: ILR School Extension Division Residential Study Institute Additional Records /4115: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4136m: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4233m: ILR School Western Regional Office Records /4239: ILR School Extension Registrar's Office Student Data Collection Forms /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio- Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo,N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
Labor unions--Organizing; Union busting; Video display terminals; Collective labor agreements; Sick building syndrome; Radon; Sexual harassment; Employee fringe benefit; Retirement--Planning; Arbitration, Industrial; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
6876497
- Placid Harbor, 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  V164
- Permanent Damage? Health hazards in Beauty Salons, 2 (Box 1)
  V165
- Lo Que Usted Dice Quento, 3 (Box 1)
  V182
- Measuring Radon in Structures, 4 (Box 1)
  V158
- National Training Fund "Medical Effects of Asbestos - 8/13/1987, 5 (Box 1)
  V160
- Losing the War with Japan, 6 (Box 1)
  V150
- LTV Report 15 -- May, 1986, 7 (Box 1)
  V152
- Sick Building: Sick People, 8 (Box 1)
  V169
- Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America: The Campaign for Employee Rights - A Joint Project of 1199 the National Rainbow Coalition, 9 (Box 1)
  V168
- Rochester Career and Education Expo, 10 (Box 1)
  V167
- Protect Yourself, 11 (Box 1)
  V166
- Paycheck Economics, 12 (Box 1)
  V163
- Making a Difference in Tomorrow's World, 13 (Box 1)
  V159
- FORD-UAW - AIS - Day 1/Tape 3, 14 (Box 1)
  V145
- FORD-UAW - AIS - Day 2/Tape 2, 15 (Box 1)
  V146
- ICAT Mazzochi, 16 (Box 1)
  V149
- Frontline: Losing the War with Japan, 17 (Box 1)
  also You are America -- V151
- MGF: Teleconference on ALPHA - 6/9/1992, 18 (Box 1)
  V157
- Mutual Gains Bargaining, 19 (Box 1)
  V154
- Biggest Lump of Money in the World / NBC News White Paper, 20 (Box 1)
  V155
- Labor Video Bulletin #24, 21 (Box 1)
  V153
- VDT's in the Workplace, 22 (Box 1)
  part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies -- V oversize 9
- Today's American Brass, 1 (Box 2)
  V173
- Outokumpu American Brass USWA Local 593 - Working Together for a Better Future / Sept. 1994, 2 (Box 2)
  V162
- Southern Poverty Law Center, 3 (Box 2)
  V170
- Steelmakers A Better Way of Working Together / Participative Management at LTV Steel -- April 1988, 4 (Box 2)
  V171
- Organizing the Road to dignity - UFCW, 5 (Box 2)
  V161
- Unmarked, 6 (Box 2)
- The Discipline of Teams, 7 (Box 2)
  V201
- Niagara Mohawk - Ice Storm 1998, 8 (Box 2)
  V203
- Teamster Boss: Jackie Presser, 9 (Box 2)
  V172
- Niagara Mohawk - Ice Storm 1998, 10 (Box 2)
  V202
- House Calls, 1996; 11 (Box 2)
  V180
- Former Pro Union-Buster Marty Levitt Tells All, 1996; 12 (Box 2)
  V179
- It's Your Choice, 1996; 13 (Box 2)
  V181
- RTC-015, January 1995, 14 (Box 2)
  V195
- Ready to Respond / University of Maryland, 15 (Box 2)
  V174
- Turn It Around: Teamster Stewards Solving Problems on the Job, 1994; 16 (Box 2)
  V175
- Harry Katz, 12/14/1989, 17 (Box 2)
  V148
- Every Member an Organizer, 1986; 18 (Box 2)
  V178
- A Strong Union Involves Everyone, 1995; 19 (Box 2)
  V177
- Power at Work: Building a Teamster Member-to-Member Action Network, 1997; 20 (Box 2)
  V190
- Syracuse Supply Company: Financing Arrangements, 1 (Box 3)
  V82
- Syracuse Supply Expose, 2 (Box 3)
  V81
- There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994; 3 (Box 3)
  V87
- There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994; 4 (Box 3)
  V86
- There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994; 5 (Box 3)
  V85
- There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994; 6 (Box 3)
  V84
- There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994; 7 (Box 3)
  V83
- Office of the Future, 8 (Box 3)
  V62
- The Out Group - 1991, 9 (Box 3)
  V65
- Outokumpu American Brass Training TogetherOur Competitive Edge / September 1995, 10 (Box 3)
  V66
- Operative Systems - Moc Training, Dr. Sean McAlinden Globalnomics From Craft to Mass to Modern, 11 (Box 3)
  V60
- Nummi KQED Show, 12 (Box 3)
- Shift Change Preview, 13 (Box 3)
- The Road to Solidarity: The Story of Solidarity Christmas, 1989 / produced by UAW Region 9, 1990, 14 (Box 3)
  V71
- Mandela: The Man and His Country, 1 (Box 4)
  V218
- Pixel Mojo - Time Flies, 2 (Box 4)
- WTC Forum - 9/21/2001, 3 (Box 4)
- Vision Into the New Century, November 1996, 4 (Box 4)
  V212
- With Babies and Banners, 5 (Box 4)
  V108
- Cornell ILR, 6 (Box 4)
- Saturn in the Classroom - J. Walline; UAW 6M Teacher Center Network; One More Victim, 7 (Box 4)
- Surrounded / Health hazards Associated with Electromagnetic Fields, 8 (Box 4)
  V80
- Surrounded / Health hazards Associated with Electromagnetic Fields, 9 (Box 4)
  V79
- Solidarity UAW, 10 (Box 4)
  V75
- Fleetwood, 11 (Box 4)
  V70
- Old Ways, New Game, 12 (Box 4)
  V61
- ADVR-205-V, 13 (Box 4)
  V63
- Reckoning: The Political Economy of Canada, Shift Change / Part Two, 14 (Box 4)
  V73
- Recruiting the Diversified Workforce, 15 (Box 4)
  V227
- SteelThe Backbone of America, 16 (Box 4)
  V228
- Worker Adjustment to the Global Economy: A Dynamic Learning Program for Union Leaders, Educators, and Workers, 17 (Box 4)
  Videos for Module 1 and Module 8 -- [2 tapes in one case]
- Lead at Your Own Risk: Colombian Labor's Struggle Against Violence and Corporate Globalizations, 1 (Box 5)
  V233
- MMUC Plant Introduction / April 1990, 2 (Box 5)
- Mandela: Labor Relations, 3 (Box 5)
- American Dream, 4 (Box 5)
  V211
- 1877: The Grand of Starvation, 5 (Box 5)
  V210
- Modern Times, 6 (Box 5)
- Slim The Lineman, 7 (Box 5)
  V205
- Right The First Time, 8 (Box 5)
- Keynote Speeches - Democratic National Convention -- New York, New York / July 1992, 9 (Box 5)
- Domestic Violence: Unions Respond with Blur Effect Only, 10 (Box 5)
- Jimmy Hoffa Interview -- 4/1975, 11 (Box 5)
  Long version
- Sit Down Strike! Walter Reuther and the Rise of the UAW, 12 (Box 5)
  V223
- Nabisco Niagara Falls Bakery: 100 Years of Excellence, 1901-2001, 13 (Box 5)
  V231
- D.W. Griffith's Intolerance, 14 (Box 5)
  V216
- MEEZT on Common Ground: Speaking Up for Respect in the Workplace, 15 (Box 5)
- Would You Cross a Picket Line? / Workers Defense League, 16 (Box 5)
  V221
- Best-In-Class, 17 (Box 5)
  V220
- Final Offer: UAW and the Auto Industry, 18 (Box 5)
- BLS Graduation 2002 / Arthur Eve, 19 (Box 5)
- Niagara Mohawk - Ice Storm -- 1998, 20 (Box 5)
  V204
- Made in America? / Parts I-IV, 21 (Box 5)
  V57
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 1 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 2 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 3 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 4 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 5 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 6 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 7 (Box 6)
- Yoga for Stress Reduction, 8 (Box 6)
- The Hidden Danger, 9 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 10 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 11 (Box 6)
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 12 (Box 6)
- Frontline: American Game, Japanese Rules, 13 (Box 6)
  V43
- VDTS in the Workplace: part I-Health Concerns; part 2-Strategies, 14 (Box 6)
- Labor Parade - 1989, 15 (Box 6)
  V51
- History: 1960-1973 -- Japan/Oil, 16 (Box 6)
  V46
- Crisis in the Workplace, 1 (Box 7)
  V32
- Changing Attitudes: Union Members Talk About AIDS, 2 (Box 7)
  V25
- Changing Attitudes: Union Members Talk About AIDS, 3 (Box 7)
  V24
- The Case of the Safety and Health Hazards / Narrated by Raymond Burr, 4 (Box 7)
  V20
- The Case of the Safety and Health Hazards / Narrated by Raymond Burr, 5 (Box 7)
  V18
- Continuous protection fro Ladder Climbing and Scaffold Maintenance, 6 (Box 7)
  V31
- Bargaining 1992, 7 (Box 7)
  V33
- Supervis, 8 (Box 7)
- Buffalo Labor Studies, 9 (Box 7)
  V13
- Jim Harbour: Saginawa Mi - Bug Conf., 10 (Box 7)
  V50
- Brass Valley: Brass Workers History Project, 11 (Box 7)
  V7
- Ford Tapes, Focus on Selling Technology, Pts. I II -- The Escort: Frontline Reports Fcn, January 1992, 12 (Box 7)
  V42
- Frontline: American Game, Japanese Rules, 13 (Box 7)
- From Drawing Board to Delivery, 14 (Box 7)
  V41
- Ford-UAW -- Generations - Recreating History, 15 (Box 7)
  V40
- Case Research in Labor Relations Reporter, 16 (Box 7)
  V16
- Labor Video Bulletin #19, 17 (Box 7)
  V53
- Ford Motor Company: 90 Years of Progress, 18 (Box 7)
  V39
- Case Research in Labor Relations Reporter, 19 (Box 7)
  V17
- Cornell Industry Education Program: Auto Industry Case Study, 20 (Box 7)
  V3
- LTV Report #23, 21 (Box 7)
  V56
- LVBT-27b-V, 22 (Box 7)
  V54
- LVBT-034-V, 23 (Box 7)
  V55
- Hiding in Plain Sight (Electromagnetic fields), 24 (Box 7)
  V45
- Construction Organizing: Lessons of the Past and the Challenges Ahead, 25 (Box 7)
  V30
- Computers in Context, 1 (Box 8)
  V29
- Did You Know?, 2 (Box 8)
  V35
- Fall Protection, 3 (Box 8)
  V37
- Cornell Industry Education Program: Dimension of Competitiveness, 4 (Box 8)
  V36
- The American Experience Los Mineros, 5 (Box 8)
  English version
- Brassworker's History Project - Brass Valley, 6 (Box 8)
  V9
- How Not to Hold a Meeting, 7 (Box 8)
  V137
- Brass Valley: Brass Workers' History project, 8 (Box 8)
  Edited version -- V8
- American Brass Today's American Brass, 9 (Box 8)
- Brass Workers History Project, 10 (Box 8)
  Edit version of original -- V10
- Autoalliance International, Inc. / Plant Tour, 11 (Box 8)
  V4
- Brass Workers History Project, 12 (Box 8)
  Edit version of original -- V11
- FORD-UAW -- AIS, Day 1/Tape 1 -- 2/22/1993, 13 (Box 8)
  V144
- Buffalo Labor Studies, 14 (Box 8)
  V12
- WBUF FM-93 -- Holiday match Game Preview, 15 (Box 8)
  V136
- Internal Organizing: Planning the Campaign, 16 (Box 8)
  V134
- Internal Organizing Simulation, 17 (Box 8)
  V135
- First on the scene, 18 (Box 8)
- Clockwork, 19 (Box 8)
  V27
- Buffalo Supervisory Studies, 20 (Box 8)
  V15
- Work Solutions - Empowering Workers, 1 (Box 9)
  V110
- Work Worth Doing - Parts I II, 2 (Box 9)
  V113
- Barry Bluestone - Economics #2, 3 (Box 9)
  V117
- ADA: A Time to understand, 4 (Box 9)
  V120
- Video Magic / Ray Marshall, 5 (Box 9)
  V101
- Tech Video - Turning Tech. Around, 6 (Box 9)
  V90
- There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994; 7 (Box 9)
  V88
- Al Ketzel: Upgrading Computers, 8 (Box 9)
  V99
- Union Yes (6/1988), 9 (Box 9)
  V100
- Collective Bargaining: Session 9 -- 10/21/1986, 10 (Box 9)
  V126
- Communications Skills for Internal Organizing with Gene Morrill, 11 (Box 9)
  V131
- Working Solutions - Skill Crisis, 12 (Box 9)
  V111
- Collective Bargaining - Session 4 -- 9/16/1986, 13 (Box 9)
  V125
- Avid Productions - Video Co., 14 (Box 9)
  V123
- With Babies Banners, 15 (Box 9)
  V106
- ABC's 20-20 Saginaw, 16 (Box 9)
  V114
- Working in the 1990s, 17 (Box 9)
  V109
- A Walk through the 20th Century: America on the road, 18 (Box 9)
  V104
- America on the road: Episode 11, 19 (Box 9)
  V103
- With Babies and Banners, 20 (Box 9)
  V107
- Call Me Sister, call me brother, 21 (Box 9)
  V119
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992), 1 (Box 10)
  tape 1 of 8 -- V91
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992), 2 (Box 10)
  tape 2 of 8 -- V92
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992), 3 (Box 10)
  tape 3 of 8 -- V93
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992), 4 (Box 10)
  tape 4 of 8 -- V94
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992), 5 (Box 10)
  tape 5 of 8 -- V95
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992), 6 (Box 10)
  tape 6 of 8 -- V96
- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Unions in 1992 (Conference 9/30-10/2/1992, 7 (Box 10)
  Roundtable Discussions #2 --tape 7 of 8 -- V97
- 1949 Bell Strike -- UAW/Bell Aircraft Strike of 1949: Its Impact on Union in 1992, 8 (Box 10)
  tape 8 of 8 -- V98
- Macacademy - Word Tape 1, 9 (Box 10)
  VHS
- Macacademy - Word Tape 2, 10 (Box 10)
- Macacademy -- Word Tape 3, 11 (Box 10)
- Macacademy -- Word Tape 4, 12 (Box 10)
- Japan they didn't talk about, 13 (Box 10)
- Ford design technology, 14 (Box 10)
- VDT's in the workplace - Part 1 - Health concerns, 15 (Box 10)
- VDT's in the workplace - Part 2 - Strategies, 16 (Box 10)
- VW Golf, 17 (Box 10)
- NYS Dept. Social Svcs. - Stress Mgmt., 1 (Box 11)
- Ready or Not -, 2 (Box 11)
- Preparation for Retirement - Session I - the meaning of, 3 (Box 11)
- VDT's in the "Workplace -- Part 2 - Strategies, 4 (Box 11)
- Preparation for Retirement - Session 4 - Maintaining Health, 5 (Box 11)
- Women Workers in Western NY, 6 (Box 11)
- A New Freedom, 7 (Box 11)
- A New Freedom - For preview, 8 (Box 11)
- Pre-Retirement Preparation - Session IV; Maintaining Health, 9 (Box 11)
  edited 3/3/1978 - unfinished U-Matic
- Mock Mediation: Phoenix, 1 (Box 12)
- NLRB: Mock Case Hearing #2, 2 (Box 12)
- Clockwork, 3 (Box 12)
- Manufacturing Miracles, 4 (Box 12)
- Buffalo Labor Studies: Public Service TV Spots, 5 (Box 12)
- Buffalo Labor, 6 (Box 12)
- NLRB: Mock Case Hearing #1, 7 (Box 12)
- Supernis, 8 (Box 12)
- Buffalo Supervisory Studies, 9 (Box 12)
- McDonald - Internal Customer Satisfaction Surveys, 10 (Box 12)
- Buffalo Supervisory Studies: Public Service TV Spot, 11 (Box 12)
- Crisis in the workplace, 1 (Box 13)
- Helping adults learn - Unit 1 - How and why adults learn, 2 (Box 13)
- Brass Workers History Project, 3 (Box 13)
  Edited version of original -- Edit MASTER
- Buffalo Supervisory Studies: Public Service TV Spots, 4 (Box 13)
- Buffalo labor Studies: Public Service TV Spot, 5 (Box 13)
- Buffalo Labor Studies: Public Service TV Spots, 6 (Box 13)
- Helping Adults Learn - Unit 2 - Getting off to a good, 7 (Box 13)
- Supervisory Series and Buffalo Labor Series, 8 (Box 13)
  2 open reel tapes in one box
- ABC 20/20, 9 (Box 13)
- The Eye of the Beholder (Box 14)
  - The Eye of the Beholder, 1 (Box 14)
- The Rest of Your Life (Box 15)
  - The Rest of Your Life, 1 (Box 15)
- Mediation in Action for Western District Office -- 2/11/1969 (Box 16)
  - Mediation in Action for Western District Office - 2/11/1969, 1 (Box 16)
- Mediation in Action -- Produced by Western Dist., NYSSILR -- 4/11/1968 (Box 17)
  - Mediation in Action - Produced by Western Dist., NYSSILR, 1 (Box 17)
- Unmarked, 1 (Box 18)
- The Essential New York Initiative, 2 (Box 18)
- Health Care Critical Condition -- 8/28/1990, 3 (Box 18)
- Collision Course (PEL), 4 (Box 18)
- The Case of Barbara Parson, 5 (Box 18)
- NLMCC?IBEW-NECA 2000 -- Partnering Video, 6 (Box 18)
- Ford Communications Network: UAW Panel Discussion - Part 2 -- 4/28/2000, 7 (Box 18)
- Ford Communications Network -- UAW/Ford Panel -- 3/22/2000, 8 (Box 18)
- Meeting Your Challenge as a New Trustee, 9 (Box 18)
- Ford Communications Network -- UAW Panel Discussion - Part 2 -- 4/28/2000, 10 (Box 18)
- Ford communications Network - UAW/Ford Panel -- 3/22/2000, 11 (Box 18)
- Ford Communications Network - UAW/Ford Panel -- 3/22/2000, 12 (Box 18)
- UAW/Ford-Cornell - Labor Relations Video Segments 1,2, 3 and Raws - Answers Only -- 5/16/2000, 13 (Box 18)
- Unmarked, 14 (Box 18)
- Yvonne Rebholz, 15 (Box 18)
- Yvonne Rebholz, 16 (Box 18)
- Clinton Town Meeting 2/10/1993, 17 (Box 18)
- Unmarked, 18 (Box 18)
- Cornell University -- Presidents address to Congress - 2/1993, 19 (Box 18)
- Unmarked, 20 (Box 18)
- Presidential Debate #1 -- 10/11/1992, 21 (Box 18)
- Unmarked, 22 (Box 18)
- Unmarked slides, 1 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 2 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 3 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 4 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 5 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 6 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 7 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 8 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 9 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 10 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 11 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 12 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 13 (Box 19)
- Revised slide presentation for GM/UAW Programs - 8/7/1988, 14 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 15 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 16 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 17 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 18 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 19 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 20 (Box 19)
- From the Past to the Present, 21 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 22 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 23 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 24 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 25 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 26 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 27 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 28 (Box 19)
- Unmarked slides, 29 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for General Service Workers, 30 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for General Service Workers, 31 (Box 19)
- Chemical Safety for General Service Workers, 32 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 33 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 34 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 35 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 36 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 37 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 38 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit I, 39 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit II, 40 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit II, 41 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit III, 42 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit III, 43 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit III, 44 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit III, 45 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit III, 46 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit III, 47 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit IV, 48 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit IV, 49 (Box 19)
- Recognizing Identifying Hazardous Mat'l. Unit IV, 50 (Box 19)
- Cornell Campus Slides (1983), 51 (Box 19)
- Heat Stress Slides, 52 (Box 19)
- Unmarked -- (found 8/11/2000), 53 (Box 19)
- Office Workers, 54 (Box 19)
- Office Workers, 55 (Box 19)
- Office Workers, 56 (Box 19)
- Office Workers, 57 (Box 19)
- Office Workers, 58 (Box 19)
- Office Workers, 59 (Box 19)
- Economics and Political World we organize in, 60 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 61 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 62 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 63 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 64 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 65 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 66 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 67 (Box 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary, 68 (Box 19)
- Power Sharing at Daimler-Benz, 1 (Box 20)
- Surviving the bottom line: Living on the fault line, 2 (Box 20)
- Surviving the bottom line: beating the bottom line, 3 (Box 20)
- Special Wage Reporting, 4 (Box 20)
- The Employer's Perspective, 5 (Box 20)
- Surviving the bottom line: running with the Bulls, 6 (Box 20)
- Business and Commerce, 7 (Box 20)
- Labor's Future in the Global Economy / Gus Tyler, 8 (Box 20)
- Selecting and Preparing Reports, 9 (Box 20)
  tape five
- Remember for TomorrowA History of OCAW International Union, 10 (Box 20)
- Employer Year End Reporting Completing and Filing W-2/W-3 Annual Wage Reports, 11 (Box 20)
- Crisis in the workplace, 12 (Box 20)
- Changing the way we work an America works special, 13 (Box 20)
- Video to accompany: Interpersonal Skills in Organizations, 2002; 14 (Box 20)
- Video to accompany: Interpersonal Skills in Organizations, 2002; 15 (Box 20)
- Video to accompany: Interpersonal Skills in Organizations, 2002; 16 (Box 20)
- Video to accompany: Interpersonal Skills in Organizations, 2002; 17 (Box 20)
- Video to accompany: Interpersonal Skills in Organizations, 2002; 18 (Box 20)
- A New Freedom, 1 (Box 21)
- A Week Full of Saturdays, 2 (Box 21)
- Mediation in Action, 3 (Box 21)
- Ford Communications Network, 4 (Box 21)
- Advancing the World of Work (11/8/2000) -- CD 1 of 2 (Box 22)
  - Advancing the World of Work (11/8/2000), 1 (Box 22)
    CD 1 of 2
- Advancing the World of Work (11/8/2000) -- CD 2 of 2 (Box 23)
  - Advancing the World of Work (11/8/2000), 1 (Box 23)
    CD 2 of 2
- ADT Security Services: A Labor Relations Primer (Box 24)
  - ADT Security Services: A Labor Relations Primer, 1 (Box 24)
- An Introduction to Scientology (Box 25)
  - An Introduction to Scientology, 1 (Box 25)
- An Introduction to Scientology (Box 26)
  - An Introduction to Scientology, 1 (Box 26)
- Stop Workplace Violence (Box 27)
  - Stop Workplace Violence, 1 (Box 27)
- Buffalo Labor Programs: Women at Work -- DVD 1of 6 (Box 28.1)
  - Buffalo Labor programs: Women at Work, 1 (Box 28)
    DVD 1-6
- Buffalo Labor Programs: Women at Work -- DVD 2 of 6 (Box 28.2)
- Buffalo Labor Programs: Women at Work -- DVD 3 of 6 (Box 28.3)
- Buffalo Labor Programs: Women at Work -- DVD 4 of 6 (Box 28.4)
- Buffalo Labor Programs: Women at Work -- DVD 5 of 6 (Box 28.5)